The first thing you're going to want to do is download the Mac
你要做的第一件事是下载 Mac
or if you're working with Linux, download the Linux installation of Visual Studio code.
或者如果你用的是 Linux 的话，就下载 Linux 版本的 Visual Studio Code 安装包
Once you have it installed, it'll look a little something like this.
一旦你完成了安装，它看起来就是这样的
And if it's a fresh installation,
如果是新安装的
It'll even give you some tips and tools to actually get started.
它还会在你开始使用前提供一些提示和工具
If you've never worked with Visual Studio code before,
如果你之前从来没使用过 Visual Studio Code
I highly recommend going through any get started or getting instructions tips that come with opening Visual Studio Code.
我强烈建议你浏览一下 Visual Studio Code 打开时出现的入门和指导技巧
Additionally, we have a Visual Studio Code crash course
此外，我们还提供了一个 Visual Studio Code 速成课
in the GitHub repo associated with this course.
就在本课程关联的 Github 仓库中
Once you have Visual Studio code installed,
安装好 Visual Studio Code 后
the next thing that we're going to want to install is going to be node j s.
下一个要安装的东西是 Node.js
And again, we have links to all of these in the GitHub repo associated with this course,
重要的事说三遍，所有这些链接我们都放到了课程关联的 Github 仓库里
you can just go ahead and click download for Mac OS or download for Linux,
你可以点击下载 Mac OS 版本或者下载 Linux 版本
I recommend using the LTS version.
我建议使用这个 LTS 版本
lts stands for long term support, which means that they will be supporting this version for a long time.
LTS 表示长期支持(long term support)，意思就是他们会长期支持这个版本
So go ahead and download Node js. I've already downloaded this,
我们继续，下载 Node.js，我这里已经下载过了
so I'm not gonna go ahead and redownload this
所以我就不重新下载一遍了
now one of the awesome things about Visual Studio code is it has this thing called terminals,
Visual Studio Code 一个很棒的地方是它有终端
which are command line prompts that allow us to run scripts,
终端就是命令行提示符，能够让我们运行脚本
basically, it's where we're going to be running all of our code
基本上来说，它就是我们运行所有代码的地方
where we can open up the terminal is we can go ahead and hit terminal
我们可以在这里点击“终端” (Terminal)
and select new terminal
然后选择 “新建终端” (New Terminal)
and you'll get something like this.
然后你会得到这样的东西
Now you might have bash or Z ca or some other type of shell
现在你可能是 bash 或者 zsh 或是其他类型的某种 shell
type that you have doesn't really matter because on Mac and Linux it's going to be Linux based
你拥有的是什么类型并不重要，因为在 Mac 和 Linux 上，终端都是基于 Linux 的
we can now test our no Jess installation
我们现在可以测试 node.js 的安装结果
has been done correctly by running Node dash dash version,
通过运行 node --version 来确定安装是否正确完成
and you should see something that looks like this.
你应该能看到类似这样的东西
The exact version of node that you have doesn't really matter here.
这里 node 具体是什么版本并不是很重要
But ideally you're at least on Node version 14 or higher.
但版本至少要是 14 或者更高才会比较理想
And if something like this doesn't show up, remember to go ahead and start looking at Stack Overflow
如果这些输出并没有出现的话，记得去看看 Stack Overflow
looking on the GitHub repo in the discussions tab, looking on the updated section, etc.
以及 Github 仓库的讨论区，还有查看里面的章节更新，等等等等
And like I said, sometimes installing this can be the hardest part of this entire course so,
就像我说的，有时候安装就是整个课程最难的一部分
so don't get discouraged.
所以不要气馁
And please use Stack Overflow Stack Exchange Etherium, and the GitHub repo
去 Stack Overflow, Stack Exchange Etherium, 以及 Github 仓库
to move past any issues you run into.
来解决你遇到的所有问题
Now, if you're on Mac or Linux,
现在，如果你使用的是 Mac 或者 Linux，
you can actually hit Ctrl back tick, to actually toggle your terminal mode,
那么你可以按 Ctrl + ` (反引号) 来切换终端模式 (译者注：反引号即 `, Tab 之上 Esc 之下的和波浪线捆绑的按键)
this will pull the terminal up and down for you
它可以让你的终端在显示和隐藏两种视图中进行切换
getting familiar with keyboard shortcuts will actually make your life a lot easier.
熟悉键盘快捷键可以让你的工作生活更加轻松
Because you'll be able to move around Visual Studio code much more effectively,
因为这可以让你在使用 Visual Studio Code 时更高效
we have a link to a list of keyboard shortcuts.
我们有一个键盘快捷键列表的链接
Additionally, in the GitHub repository associated with this section,
就在与这一章节关联的 Github 仓库里
as we move along, I'll give tip on different keyboard shortcuts
随着我们的深入，我会给出一些不同的键盘快捷键技巧
that you can optionally use otherwise,
你可以按需选择使用
you can just go ahead and click as well,
你也可以通过点击来实现这些功能
you can click the trash can to delete the terminal,
你可以点击这个垃圾桶图标来删除终端
go back up Terminal new terminal to pop it back up.
之后再点击“终端” (Terminal) “新建终端” (New Terminal) 来把它弹出来
Now the next thing that we're going to need a little bit later, we're not going to need it for this section,
我们之后会用到另一个东西，但不是在现在这个章节
but it's good to install it now is going to be git
不过最好还是现在把它给装好，它就是 Git
no jazz is known as a JavaScript runtime.
Node.js 被称为 JavaScript runtime
And it's a tool that we're going to use to help run JavaScript code in our Visual Studio Code
它是一个我们用来在 Visual Studio Code 中运行 JavaScript 代码的工具
slot exactly JavaScript.
它并不完全是 JavaScript
And the difference between no Jas and JavaScript can be a little bit confusing,
而且 node.js 和 JavaScript 的区别比较混乱
but don't let that stop you for now.
但不要因为这个而让你在此止步
Next, we're actually going to go ahead and install Git,
接下来我们将继续安装 Git
we will have links to the installation instructions in the GitHub repository,
我们在 Github 仓库中提供了安装说明的链接
installing git on Linux, you're going to use one of these two commands
在 Linux 上安装 Git，你需要使用这两条命令的其中之一
and on macOS, if you just type git on the command line,
而在 Mac OS 上，如果你直接在命令行中输入 git
it should go ahead and prompt you to install it.
那么它应该就会提示你去安装它
So we're back in our command line, and we just type git, it should prompt you to go ahead and stall it.
现在我们回到我们的命令行，然后我们输入 git，它应该就会提示你安装
And if you do get dash dash version,
如果你输入 git --version
you should get something that looks like this.
你应该会得到类似这样的东西
You can also use a Mac OS get installer by clicking this link here and running through the installation process.
你也可以在 Mac OS 上从这个链接获得安装包并运行安装过程
Alright, now that you have no JS yet in Visual Studio code installed,
好了，现在你已经安装好了 node.js git 和 Visual Studio Code
we can continue on to the next section.
我们可以继续下一节了